你们中间的一位会在今夜被淘汰
And one of you will be eliminated tonight.
肖恩 我们从你开始
Sean, we're gonna start with you.
给我们讲讲你的红毯金属造型
Tell us about your red carpet metallic look.
我决定表达一种更艺术的红毯秀
I decided to go for a more artistic red carpet.
也许是见面会
Maybe at the met.
这里使用了一种黄油伦敦的颜色
There was one of the butter london colors,
玫瑰金 像是珊瑚
Which was this rose goldy, like coral,
用作基础颜色
Which, kind of used as my base.
这种疯狂的流苏裙惊讶到我了
It surprised us with this kind of mad fringe skirt,
它正真衬托出了面料
Which really sets off the fabric.
我得到了整个十九世纪
I'm getting a whole 19th century,
有种 日蹦 风格的礼服
Sort of japonais-like thing.
-你说 日本？ - 是啊
-You said "Japonais"? -Yeah, I did.
-好吧 应该是 - 你在说什么？
-Well, it's like or-or... -Who are you?
我在说什么？ -日本人
who am I? -Japanese.
不是 Ais
No, but like, as in "Ais,"
因为你不能这么说 一个日本人
'cause you can't say, like, “a La japanese."
首先 我喜欢折纸效果
Well, first of all, I love the origami effect.
这很日本风
-It's very japonais. -
然后 如果它是中短裙就更好了
However, I would love this if it was mid-thigh.
我需要显现更多的腿
I need more leg.
对我来说 上面对比下面显得太沉重
For me, the top is too heavy for the bottom.
-现在 请你转一圈 那就很均衡了
-Now, if you turn around, that's a beautiful balance.
如此优雅 颜色又如此微妙
It's so elegant and the colors are just exquisite.
我喜欢你带来的这种帝国风
I love this empire line that you've given us,
抽象的裙子 并且它的颜色很特别
With this abstract peplum, and the color is very special.
从每个角度看都很有趣
It's interesting from every angle,
这对于红毯来说非常重要
Which is also very important for the red carpet.
-安雅 -我决定
-Anya. -I decided to go
走稍微有条理的方向
In a slightly more structured direction.
因为我想的是一种格莱美伸展台
Because I thought of a grammys runway.
那种让人感到紧张的情况
It's something that is a bit more edgy.
我想要做得不一样
I wanted to do something a lot different.
当你展示出来 给我的第一印象是
When you walked out, the first thing I thought was,
我不懂你的点
"I don't get it."
这是红毯秀 而不是伸展台
It's a red carpet look, not a runway.
叉腰 你觉得如何？
Hand on your hip, how does that look?
你明白我说的 我感觉 很疑惑
You know what I mean, I feel like, eh, it's confused.
因为把袖子做成这样是十分冒险的
'cause it's super risky to make sleeves like that,
因为很多人都会直接感觉 像是
'cause so many people are gonna instantly be, like,
我喜欢或者我讨厌它
I love it or I hate it.
我认为 你有些很好的地方
I think, whilst you had some really good things,
像是颜色和布料
Like the color and the fabric,
袖子有点让我失望
The sleeves kind of wreck it for me.
温蒂 你同意艾萨克的观点吗？
Wendy, do you agree with isaac?
-不 我不同意
-No, I don't.
我喜欢这套衣服
I love that dress.
我觉得穿上很好看
I could pull that off.
40英寸的腿 还有长且抽象的袖子
40-Inch legs, those long, dramatic sleeves.
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
不 我必须得指出
no, and I do have to point out
从结构的角度来看
That from a construction standpoint,
我与我的设计同行们差得很远
I really am a wide sea away from my fellow designers.
我在最后时刻得到了很多帮助
I got a lot of help at the last minute today.
并且还有很多需要修改的
And it has a lot to do with editing.
这件衣服需要从设计开始考虑
This dress has to start with the design.
你需要想象一个女人
You've got to think of a woman
从每一个角度被拍照
Being photographed from every angle,
我认为现在不适合
And I just don't think that's the moment
说那样的话
For a statement like that.
依琳娜 说说你的红毯时装的质感
Irina, tell us about the texture in your red carpet look.
她是要去奥斯卡或者金球奖的晚会
she's either going to the oscars or the golden globes
我十分幸运
And I was lucky enough
找到了这个 令人兴奋的亮片
To find this, sort of, interesting sequin
它的两种光影像是一种
Where it has, like, two shades in one.
我把它挂起来 有点雕刻的意思
But I draped it and I sort of sculpted it.
这种面料选得太好了
It's a really great fabric choice.
请为我们转一圈好吗？
Can you turn around, please, for us?
从后面看很漂亮 你知道  他们喜欢
It's beautiful from the back. You know, because they love
-过肩拍摄 -对
-Those over-the-shoulder shots. -Yeah.
真是太美了
this is so beautiful.
以及口袋和衬里 我说完了
And the pockets and the lining, I'm done.
它看起来有点重
it does look a little heavy,
但是 总体来说 很漂亮
But I think, overall, it's beautiful,
我特别喜欢 胸围线
And I love particularly, the bust line.
我喜欢这种直接剪裁
I love that straight cut.
它给人感觉上半部分毛绒绒的 这很雅致
It almost feels furry at the top, which is chic, you know.
像是 有点 迷彩皮毛亮片
It's like, a kind of, like, camouflage fur of sequins.
悬挂的亮片 礼服的颜色 我喜欢这种质感
The draping, the color of the dress, I love the texture.
看起来很仙女 我喜欢
It's just divine. I love it.
谢谢 莉莉
Thank you, lily.
姜果 -我用了这种红霞的颜色
django. -I used this blush color
并且有种下雨的质感
And there's this rain-like texture in it,
所以有种怀旧感 但同时也有现代感
So it has this really nostalgic but also this modern feel to me.
我感觉有点过了 当她站在这里的时候
It's actually grown on me, a bit, since it's been stood here.
我感觉当她走路的时候
I think when she was walking,
这种轮廓会让走路变得困难
I found the silhouette very difficult.
搭在背上的披肩
The cape part attached to the back
没有足够的气息来彰显她的轮廓
Didn't give enough breath to show her silhouette.
我喜欢这种背照
I love the back shot.
我不是剪开风格的粉丝
I'm not a fan of cutouts.
我希望能够全部放开
I wish that they would all go away.
当你走红毯时 没有哪里
When you walk the red carpet, uh, there's nowhere
会触碰你的皮肤 或是拉拽
That it grabs the skin, and pulls it in
或是给你提供维度
And gives you any dimension.
它看上去很重
It feels heavy.
我不知道那是什么 像是
I don't know what it is, like...
也许接触身体太多
Maybe it has too much body.
内衬 内衬
lining, lining, lining.
-比德儿 好久不见 -你好 阿莉莎
-Hi, biddell. It's been a few weeks. -Hi, alyssa.
我第一次呆在安全区
Well, I was here the first time and then I've been safe,
但我来不是为了表现得小心翼翼
And I didn't come here to play it safe.
所以我想制造一种光滑的质感
So I thought to create texture out of something smooth
这样会很有趣 我挑选了这些耳环
Would be interesting. Then I made the earrings
因为我们有更多的预算
Because we did have a bigger budget,
所以我可以这么做
So I was able to do that.
我感觉像是凯特布兰切特穿上这身礼服在走红毯
I can see cate blanchett on a red carpet in this dress.
我喜欢这种完全不同的形状
And I love how it is completely a different shape,
不论从哪个角度来看
From every angle.
如果你给我一副胸和一个深背 我一定要穿这件
If you give me side boob and a deep back, I am in.
我认为前面的线条很漂亮
I think the lines in the front are beautiful
并且这些耳环真的好看
And I adore the earrings. I really do.
我认为他们很搭
I just think that pulls it all together.
当这身礼服出来时 这里有些大小的问题
There's something about the size of it, that when it came out,
我所看到的是耳环一直在碰撞肩膀
All I could look at was the earrings, like, hitting here.
就想法而言 跟姜果礼服相差无几
It's not unlike django's dress, in terms of the idea
很窄的前身和飘逸的后背
Of a kind of small front with a very floaty back.
但是你做到了因为我们看到了更多的身体
And somehow you got it because we see more of her body.
对我来说 布料看起来很奢华
the fabric, for me, while it does look luxe,
这是不可原谅的
It is unforgiving.
-米歇尔 -当我想到金属和质感时
-Michelle. -When I think of metallic and texture,
我想到了60年代的绗缝长连衣裙
I think of the 1960s quilted maxi dress
我想把它变得更现在一些 更轻一些
And I wanted to take it in a more modern, less heavy way.
她像是很酷的女生
She's that cool girl going
去参加艺术馆开馆红毯
To an opening of a gallery red carpet.
并不一定是要去拿奖
Not necessarily going to an awards.
在红毯上 横条纹是非常难的
Horizontal stripes are super hard on a red carpet
因为它会把身体分割成很多部分
Because it's cutting the body off in so many places.
你的下摆？ 这可让我很疑惑
And that hem? That really confuses me. What...?
对 我想露出一点她的脚
Yeah, I wanted her little toes to poke out.
如果你想用直线条纹
If you're working with linear lines...
又突然在下面截断
...To suddenly put a curve at the bottom,
看起来就像是失误
It looks like a mistake.
我愿意穿这身去音乐节
I would wear this and, uh, go to a music festival
享受我的时光
And have the time of my life.
如果有空调在下方
If there's air conditioning in the fabric...
完全地 你有足够的口袋装你的物品
Totally. You have pockets for all your good things.
用口袋装下所有的东西
Pockets for all my stuff.
我在里面寻找生活 我在寻找流行音乐
I'm looking for the life in it. I'm looking for the pop.
我知道有些质感像是这样
And I know that there's some texture and things like that,
但我感觉就是有些
But I just feel like it's just kind of got that...
你在刻意装饰这些像蛇一样的图案和蕾丝
your aim here is to try to make the snake and the lace
并且将黄绿色融入这种有机的条纹里
And the chartreuse into an organic kind of stripe.
它不是有机的感觉
And it doesn't feel organic.
有点强迫的感觉
It feels forced.
谢谢 评委们
Thank you, judges.
-谢谢 米歇尔 -谢谢
-And thank you, michelle. -Thanks.
谢谢我们的设计者 也谢谢我们的模特
Thank you to our designers and thank you to your models.
你们可以回后台休息室了 谢谢
You can wait in the backstage lounge. Thank you.